/* eslint max-len: 0 */
const questions = {
  general: [
    {
      question: `What should I do if I cannot log in to my account?`,
      answer: `Please check your phone to ensure that you are connected to the internet. Then check to make sure your email address and password were entered correctly. If you're having difficulty remembering your password, please follow these steps: For iPhone, please tap the "More" button and tap "Sign in." Below the gray "Sign in" button, tap "Forgot Password?" For Android, please tap the upper right three-dot symbol and select "Sign In." Below the gray "Sign In" button, press "Forgot Password?" From there, enter the email address associated with your Chick-fil-A account. You will then have the option to have a one-time passcode emailed to you or to answer a security question associated with your account. If you cannot remember the answer to your security quetsion, please select to have a one-time password emailed to you. If you choose to have a one-time password emailed to you, please be sure to check all folders in case the email does not arrive in your inbox in a timely manner.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I order ahead to dine-in or pick-up in the drive-thru?`,
      answer: `New Dine-in and drive-thru options are coming in 2017.`
    },
    {
      question: `Why doesn't my local Restaurant show up on the app?`,
      answer: `Only select locations that accept mobile orders are listed on the app. We hope to add your favorite location and many others soon.`
    },
    {
      question: `I can't create an account on the Chick-fil-A mobile app`,
      answer: `Welcome to Chick-fil-A One. Is this the first time you've created an account for Chick-fil-A using your selected email address? If you've created a Chick-fil-A account in the past, pease enter the same email address and password.`
    },
    {
      question: `What should I do if I am unable to log in to my account?`,
      answer: `Please check your phone to ensure you are connected to the internet. Then check to make sure your email address and password were entered correctly. IF you’re having difficulty remembering your password, please follow these steps to do so. For iPhones please tap the “More” button and tap “Sign In”. Below the gray “Sign In” button, press “Forgot Password?”. Enter the email address associated with your Chick-fil-A account. You will then have the option to have a one-time passcode emailed to you or to answer a security question associated with your account. If you cannot remember the answer to your security question, please select to have a one-time passcode emailed to you. If you choose to have a onetime password emailed to you, please be sure to check all folders in case the email does not arrive to your inbox in a timely manner. For Android please tap the upper right 3-dot symbol and select “Sign In”. Below the “Sign In” button, press “Forgot Password?”. Enter the email address associated with your Chick-fil-A account. You will then have the option to have a one-time passcode emailed to you or to answer a security question associated with your account. If you cannot remember the answer to your security question, please select to have a one-time password emailed to you. If you choose to have a one-time password emailed to you, please be sure to check all folders in case the email does not arrive to your inbox in a timely manner.`
    },
    {
      question: `If I change my phone, can I transfer my Chick-fil-A account to my new device?`,
      answer: `Yes, you can. Please ensure the Chick-fil-A mobile app is downloaded and installed onto your new device. Then sign-in with your existing email address and password.`
    },
    {
      question: `What does Chick-fil-A do to protect my privacy once I register for an account within the app?`,
      answer: `Chick-fil-A does not give any customer information to third parties, unless we have the express permission of the customer. Please refer to our Privacy Policy for futher details: www.chick-fil-a.com/Legal/Privacy`
    }
  ],
  features: [
    {
      question: `How do I create a Favorite order?`,
      answer: `For iPhones: Under the order tab, choose a Chick-fil-A Restaurant and Start a New Order. Select the items that you would like to order or add to your favorites. Proceed to Checkout, but before submitting your order, scroll down and select “Save  to My Favorite Order”. On the Order tab home screen, you can also select Recent Order for reordering past meals. For Android: under the Order button, chose a Chick-fil-A Restaurant and your pickup method, then tap the Next button. Select the items that you would like to order or add to your favorites. Proceed to Checkout, but before submitting your order, scroll down and select “Save to My Favorite Order”. On the order tab home screen,  you can also select Recent Order for reordering past meals.`
    },
    {
      question: `How do I select condiments when placing a mobile order?`,
      answer: `For individual items: To add condiments to your entree, please tap the image of your menu item After tapping your selected menu item, a ‘Customize’ button will appear under the menu image. You can scroll to select condiments or enter Special Instructions. Then tap ‘Add to Order’ in the upper right-hand corner. For Meals: To add condiments to your meal, please tap the image of your menu item. After adding your chosen drink, select your entree item and scroll down to choose or remove your condiment. Then tap ‘Add to Meal’ in the upper right-hand corner.`
    },
    {
      question: `I noticed an item was missing from my Mobile Order after I left the restaurant.`,
      answer: `Please contact CARES (http://www.chick-fil-a.com/Connect/Contact-Us-CARES or 1-866-CFA-2040) with your name & contact info, location, & time of purchase. We will then provide this information to the designated restaurant Operator for further action.`
    }
  ],
  card: [
    {
      question: `How do I load money within the Chick-fil-A Mobile App?`,
      answer: `For iPhones: Sign into your account and tap “Show Card”. Next, tap “Add funds to card”. Tap on e of the predefined amount or enter an amount of your choice by tapping “Other”. Select your desired payment method from the menu: Gift Card, an existing or new credit card, Apple Pay or Visa Checkout. Tap “Reload” at the bottom of the screen. Verify your password or fingerprint to complete the transaction. If you choose not to load funds, you may also choose to add payment information prior to submitting your mobile order.

For Android: Sign into your account and select the “Show card” icon in your action bar. Tap one of the predefined amounts or enter an amount of your choice by tapping “Other”. Elect your desired payment method from the menu: Gift Card, an existing or new credit card, Android Pay or Visa Checkout. Tap “Reload” at the bottom of the screen. Verify your password or fingerprint to complete the transaction If you choose not to load funds, you may also choose to add payment information prior to submitting your mobile order.`
    },
    {
      question: `How do I save my credit card information for payments so that I don't have to enter it each time I load funds?`,
      answer: `For iPhones: Sign into your account and tap “Show card”. Next, tap “Add Funds”. Tap one of the predefined amounts or enter an amount of your choice by tapping “Other”. Select “new credit Card” from the payment options. Enter your credit card information. The “Save Card” toggle will default to “On” to save your credit card information. You may choose to disable this by toggling to “Off”. Tap “Add Card and Pay Now” at the bottom to complete the transaction.

For Android: Sign into your account and select the “Show card” icon in the action bar. Next, tap “Add Funds” Tap one of the predefined amount or enter an amount of your choice by tapping “Other”. Select “New credit Card” from the payment options. Enter your credit card information. The “Save Card” toggle will default to “On” to save your credit card information. You may choose to disable this by toggling to “Off”. Tap “Add Card and Pay Now” at the bottom to complete the transaction.”`
    },
    {
      question: `What is the maximum amount I can load onto my Chick-fil-A Mobile App account?`,
      answer: `The maximum load amount is $100 in a single transaction, and a customer may have a maximum account balance of $200 at any given time.`
    },
    {
      question: `Is there a minimum amount that I can load onto the Chick-fil-A Mobile App for Mobile Payment?`,
      answer: `Yes, the minimum amount that can be loaded is $10.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I use my Chick-fil-A One funds to purchase a gift card in the restaurant?`,
      answer: `Sorry, you cannot use funds from your Chick-fil-A One Digital Gift Card to buy physical gift cards. Chick-fil-A One Cards were designed to ake it more convenient for guests to enjoy Chick-fil-A food and may only be used to buy menu items.`
    },
    {
      question: `Is my credit card information protected?`,
      answer: `Yes. Our technology vendor protects credit card information with a secure platform that adheres to industry securty standards.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I load my physical gift card funds onto the Chick-fil-A app?`,
      answer: `Yes, transferring your physical Chick-fil-A gift card funds to the Chick-fil-A One App is easy. If your gift card does not have a PIN, please bring your gift card and device to a Chick-fil-A restaurant, and a team member will be able to assist you.

For iPhones: To get started, tap “Show Card”. Next, tap the “Add Funds” and select “Transfer Gift Card”. Enter the Gift Card Number and PIN found on the back of the card. Tap “Transfer Funds” to complete the transaction. Your physical card balance will be $0.00 and all funds will be available within the Chick-fil-A One App.
      
For Android: To get started, select the “My card” icon in the action bar. Next, tap “Add Funds”. Select “Transfer Gift Card” and enter the Gift Card Number and PIN found on the back of the card. Tap “Transfer Funds” to complete the transaction. Your physical card balance will be $0.00 and all funds will be available within the Chick-fil-A One app.`
    },
    {
      question: `What do I do if my credit car was charged twice for the same transaction?`,
      answer: `Please contact CARES (http://www.chick-fil-a.com/Connect/Contact-Us-CARES or 1-866-CFA-2040) with your contact information (name, email address, phone number), the date of the transaction, and the restaurant location. your refund request will be forwarded to the Chick-fil-A Operator for further action.`
    },
    {
      question: `How will I receive my receipt when I load money onto the Chick-fil-A Mobile app?`,
      answer: `A receipt will be emailed to the email address you entered for your Chick-fil-A One account.`
    },
    {
      question: `Why do i have a QR Code on my "My Card" screen?`,
      answer: `The QR code on the Chick-fil-A Mobile App acts the same as the card number or magnetic stripe on the back of a traditional Chick-fil-A gift card. It provides the account number to the register so that you can use your phone to pay at Chick-fil-A.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I still use my phone to pay if I don't have an internet connection?`,
      answer: `Yes, you can. The QR code is stored on your phone, and it will be available when you open the app. Please note that you will not receive an updated balance for your account until your internet connection is restored.`
    },
    {
      question: `How will I know my account balance after I pay with my Chick-fil-A One Card in-restaurant or submit a Mobile Order using my Chick-fil-A One Card funds?`,
      answer: `Your balance will automatically update anytime your funds are used in-restaurant or via a Mobile Order. You can always access your up-to-date balance on the "My card" screen of the App by swiping down on the screen. Additionally, you can find your transaction history by selecting "Transaction History" under the "Profiles" section.`
    },
    {
      question: `I don't remember adding funds or using funds through the Chick-fil-A One app. Can I view my transaction history in the app?`,
      answer: `Yes, you can view the past six months of your activity in the Chick-fil-A One app. First click the "My profile" icon on the home screen card and then select "transaction History" to find your actvitiy. The activity history will include details for funds added and transactions for which these funds have been used. If you have tnot added funds or submitted transactions throught eh Chick-fil-A One app in the past six months, your Transaction History will have a note stating "No Recent Transactions".`
    },
    {
      question: `What will happen if the scanner does not work when I try to pay with my phone?`,
      answer: `First, please make sure that the brightness setting on your phone is at a high level. If this doesn't allow the scanner to detect the QR code, please provide a Team Member with your Chick-fil-A One Card number, which is available from the "my card" screen by clicking the "?" in the circle in the top right corder of the screen.`
    },
    {
      question: `What should I do if I can't see the QR Code on the "My Card" screen?`,
      answer: `If you experience these or any other technical issues, close the app completely & reopen. If you have continued technical issues after closing & reopening the app, please ensure you've updated to the latest version of the Chick-fil-A One app.`
    },
    {
      question: `Where is my credit card information stored for the Chick-fil-A Mobile app?`,
      answer: `Your credit card information is not stored within the app or on your phone. We utilize a technology vendor to securely process and store all guest card details. The vendor protects credit card information with a secure platform that adheres to industry security standards.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I receive my Chick-fil-A account balance if my phone is lost or stolen?`,
      answer: `If your phone is lost or stolen, please call Chick-fil-A at (888) 232-1864 to report the issue. We will gladly freeze the balance remaining on your account until you're able to login to your device.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I load funds onto my account from the restaurant?`,
      answer: `Yes. You may load funds onto your mobile account by processing an Add Funds transaction at the restaurant. Please ask a Team Member to help process the transaction.`
    },
    {
      question: `I loaded funds to my account, by my balance is still showing $0.00 (zero) even though I received a receipt.`,
      answer: `Please ensure you're conected to the internet and allow 3-5 minutes for the display to update. If your balance is still showing $0.00, please contact CARES at 1-866-CFA-2040.`
    },
    {
      question: `I no longer want to use the Chick-fil-A One Card for payment. How can I get a refund for the money I placed on my Chick-fil-A One Card?`,
      answer: `Funds loaded to a Chick-fil-A One Digital Gift Card are not refundable, either in case or via credit to a credit card from which such funds were originally laoded. However, we are more than happy to transfer your remaining balance onto a physical Chick-fil-A gift card if you prefer to no longer use your Chick-fil-A One Mobile app.`
    },
    {
      question: `I received an error (error 500 or error 9999) when trying to use my Chick-fil-A One Card. What does that mean?`,
      answer: `These error codes mean the app had trouble communicating to the server. Please ensure you're connected to the internet and try again. If you have continued touble, please contact CARES (http://www.chick-fil-a.com/Connect/Contact-Us-CARES or 1-866-CFA-2040).`
    },
    {
      question: `How do I add my Chick-fil-A One card to my Apple Wallet?`,
      answer: `Simply navigate to the "My Card" screen and tap on the "Wallet" icon on the top left of the page. On the next page, tap "Add" on the top right. You can then confirm the addition by navigating to the Wallet App and scrolling the available cards.`
    },
    {
      question: `How do I pay for my meal using Apple Wallet?`,
      answer: `Paying with Apple Wallet works just as it does inside the app. Scan your QR-code at the restaurant when you make a purchase or let the team member know if you have a treat to redeem and then scan your QR-code.`
    },
    {
      question: `How do I delete my Chick-fil-A One Card from Apple Wallet?`,
      answer: `Please open the iOS Wallet APp. Swipe until you locate your Chick-fil-A one Card and select it by tapping the top of the card. Tap the inforamtion icon in the lower right hand corner of the screen and then tap Delete in the top left corner.`
    },
    {
      question: `Will the balance on my Chick-fil-A One Card in Apple Wallet update in real-time as I add and use funds in-restaurant or via Mobile Ordering?`,
      answer: `Your balance details will update within at least 24 hours of any transaction impacting you rbalance. As an alternative, you can always open the Chick-fil-A One App and navigate tot he "My Card" screen to determine your current balance.`
    },
    {
      question: `Will you be adding a Save to Android Pay feature for the Chick-fil-A One Card?`,
      answer: `Yes, Save to Android Pay is currently on our development roadmap for integration. Please continue to pay by scanning your Chick-fil-A One Card within the app in the meantime.`
    }
  ],
  ordering: [
    {
      question: `I downloaded the Chick-fil-A One app, and mobile ordering is not working. What do I do?`,
      answer: `Please ensure that you're logged in to your account and have been updated to the latest version of the app. If you're still seeing issues, please contact Chick-fil-A CARES at 1-866-CFA-2040.`
    },
    {
      question: `How can I tell the restaurant about my special requests?`,
      answer: `After selecting the menu item, scroll down to add or remove condiments and any add-ons. There is also a "Special Instructions" section at the bottom of the screen where you can type specific requests in this open form field.`
    },
    {
      question: `Do I have to prepay for mobile ordering? Can I use cash?`,
      answer: `Mobile orders require prepayment with debit or credit card or any stored value in your Chick-fil-A One Pay. You cannot use cash for mobile orders.`
    },
    {
      question: `How can I be sure the restaurant received my order?`,
      answer: `After you tap "I'm here", a confirmation page will display on the app when the restaurant has received your order.`
    },
    {
      question: `How do I let the restaurant know I've arrived?`,
      answer: `Tap "I'm here" on the app to notify the restaurant that you have arrived.`
    },
    {
      question: `When should I tap "I'm here"?`,
      answer: `Please tap "I'm here" when you've arrived at the restaurant. Remember that we are fast, and we want your food to be hot and fresh. So don't tap "I'm here" early. (Checking in from the parking lot is okay.)`
    },
    {
      question: `What happens if I get an error when I tap "I'm here"?`,
      answer: `We apologize that you received an error. Notify any Chick-fil-A team member that you have a mobile order and received an error at check-in. They will process your order and bring your food to you.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I go through the drive-thru to get my mobile order?`,
      answer: `If you wish to remain in  your vehicle, please choose our curbside option, if available, instead of using drive-thru. We don't want you waiting in line unnecessarily. Our curbside service allows you to relax for a moment while we finish preparing your oder.`
    },
    {
      question: `How do I change my order?`,
      answer: `You can continuously make changes to your order on the app until you submit it. If you wish to change an order after you have submitted it, please cancel your order in the app or see the cashier in the restaurant to make the change.`
    },
    {
      question: `I tried to submit my order by received an error message. Did the restaurant receive it? Will I be charged twice?`,
      answer: `We apologize that you received that error and technical difficulty. If you receive an error when submitting the order, then the restaurant has not yet received it. Please retry or come inside to place the order. your credit card is not charged until you tap "I'm here".`
    },
    {
      question: `How will I receive my receipt for a mobile order?`,
      answer: `Your receive will be sent via email.`
    },
    {
      question: `How can I get a refund if I am dissatisfied or received the wrong food order?`,
      answer: `We are sorry that you are not satisfied with your Chick-fil-A eperience. Please contact CARES (http://www.chick-fil-a.com/Connect/Contact-Us-CARES or 1-866-CFA-2040) and provide your contact information (name, address, phone number, email), and the date and location of the transaction. Your request will be forwarded to the Chick-fil-A operator for further action.`
    },
    {
      question: `I didn't see any curbside spaces in the parking lot. How will you find me?`,
      answer: `If you've selected curbside delivery, Chick-fil-A team members will look for the vehicle type and color that you entered in the app. if all else fails, we will call your cell phone number.`
    },
    {
      question: `Where should I wait for carry-out orders?`,
      answer: `Please wait near the "Pickup" sign. One of our servers will find you.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I pick up an order for multiple people at my office using the app?`,
      answer: `Yes, there are two ways to pick up an order for multiple people: consolidate everyone's choices into one order, or place separate orders and use the Special Intructions field on the app to alert the restaurant that you are picking up for multiple people. Then tap "I'm here" when you arrive.`
    },
    {
      question: `Why is there not a "Dine In" option?`,
      answer: `At this time, "Carry Out" or "Curbside Pickup" are the only options for mobile orders.`
    },
    {
      question: `Is there a way to create a "Favorite Restaurant" rather than the closest location?`,
      answer: `Not yet, but we're working on it.`
    },
    {
      question: `is there a way to select a different restaurant, rather than just the closest location?`,
      answer: `Yes. From the app's home screen, tap "Find" and select a location from the map.`
    }
  ],
  treats: [
    {
      question: `How do I receive a treat?`,
      answer: `The more you visit, the closer you get to treats. It's our way of saying thanks!`
    },
    {
      question: `How do I redeem a treat?`,
      answer: `Treats can be redeemd by mobile ordering through the app or by ordering the item at the front counter and sscanning your in-app QR code. A-listers can also swipe their A-List cards.`
    },
    {
      question: `Do I need to load funds to make progress toward treats?`,
      answer: `No. Simply scan the in-app QR code at the restaurant during a purchase, and you will get closer to your next treat. You can pay for your order using your credit card, cash, Chick-fil-A one funds, or a gift card.`
    },
    {
      question: `Do my treats expire?`,
      answer: `Yes, treats usually expire 30 days after they are received. Treat information can be viewed in the treats section of the app.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I receive multiple treats at a time?`,
      answer: `Yes, you can see all your treats in the 'Available Treats' section of the home screen.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I gift treats?`,
      answer: `Sorry, treats cannot be gifted.`
    },
    {
      question: `Do gift cards count towards my treats?`,
      answer: `Gift cards count towards a treat when they are *used*, but not when they are bought.`
    },
    {
      question: `When is my treat activity updated?`,
      answer: `Pleas allow 24-48 hours for your treat status to update.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I get closer to my next treat by visiting any Chick-fil-A restaurant?`,
      answer: `Yes, by licensee restaurants such as colleges, airports, hospitals etc., are excluded.`
    },
    {
      question: `Can I get treats faster by loading funds with Apple Pay?`,
      answer: `Yes. You make progress toward your next treat eery time you load funds with Apple Pay until September 10, 2016. It's just another way for us to say thanks. After loading, you'll immediately receive a notification saying that your progress will show within 24 to 48 hours.`
    },
    {
      question: `I don't use Apple Pay, how can I get treats faster?`,
      answer: `Chick-fil-A is exploring ways of thanking all Chick-fil-A One Members. We are researching creative ways to thank non-Apple-Pay users later in 2016.`
    },
    {
      question: `Where can I redeem a treat?`,
      answer: `Treats can be redeemed at any Chick-fil-A (Licensee restaurants such as colleges, airports, hospitals etc., are excluded.)`
    }
  ],
  calendar: [
    {
      question: `How do I redeem the offers from the cow calendar promotional card?`,
      answer: `Follow the steps to activate your card by signing in to your existing Chick-fil-A Account or creating a new Chick-fil-A Account.

Once the promotional card is activated, it will be loaded with the valid single-use offer(s) each month. The month of September has two offers: a Free Large Waffle Potato Fries and a Free Large Coca Cola Soft Drink of your choice. Both offers may be redeemed during the same visit or you may redeem the offers on separate visits. 
      
To redeem the offer of the month, simply bring your mobile phone with the activated 2016 calendar promotional card with you to a Chick-fil-A restaurant and present it to the team member when ordering the featured item.`
    }
  ]
};

export default questions;
